Okay, so missing records are a common issue that
حسنًا، تعد السجلات المفقودة مشكلة شائعة
you'll deal with a ton in your data wrangling career.
تواجهكم بكثرة جدًا في حياتكم المهنية في التعامل مع البيانات.
Pandas represents them as NaNs or NaN which means not a number.
تمثلها Pandas بـ NaNs أو NaN وهو ما يعني عدم وجود رقم.
These are important to be aware of as they can cause problems when coding.
وينبغي أن تكونوا على درية بهم لأنها قد تسبب مشاكل عند الترميز.
Okay then, as soon as possible,
حسنًا وبعد ذلك، في أسرع وقت ممكن،
immediately, and ASAP for a start date.
على الفور، وفي أسرع وقت ممكن "ASAP" بالنسبة لتاريخ البداية.
These all mean the same thing.
كل هذه العبارات لها نفس المعنى.
Start this job now.
لنبدأ هذا العمل الآن.
But searching for that single notion in that column
لكن البحث عن هذه الفكرة المفردة في هذا العمود
isn't easy because there are multiple ways of referring to the same thing.
ليس أمرًا سهلاً نظرًا لوجود طرق متعددة للإشارة إلى الشيء نفسه.
ASAP, immediately, as soon as possible.
ASAP, على الفور، في أسرع وقت ممكن،
Ideally, there would only be one way.
من الناحية المثالية، لن يكون هناك سوى طريقة واحدة.
Let's make a note to fix these two quality issues that we
دعونا ندون ملاحظة لإصلاح هاتين المشكلتين الخاصتين بالجودة اللتين
identified and we'll do that by inserting a new cell below here,
حددناهما وسنفعل ذلك عن طريق إدراج خلية جديدة أدناه هنا،
a markdown cell, and we'll write missing values,
خلية markdown، وسنكتب القيم المفقودة
NaN and StartDate inconsistencies.
وNaN وتناقضات StartDate.
Assessing your data is often this easy.
وغالبًا ما يكون تقييم بياناتك بهذه السهولة.
You look through it, notice glaring errors and make notes of them.
بالنظر خلال هذه العملية، تلاحظوا أخطاء صارخة وتدونون ملاحظات عليها.
In this snapshot of the data set,
في هذه اللقطة لمجموعة البيانات،
everything else seems okay.
كل شيء آخر يبدو على ما يرام.
These funky symbols here are okay since that is the original job posting with raw HTML.
تبدو هذه الرموز غير التقليدية هنا على ما يرام لأن هذا هو موضع الهمة الأصلي مع HTML خام.
These backslashes followed by letters are called
تسمى هذه الخطوط المائلة العكسية المتبوعة بالأحرف باسم
Escape Constructs and they help structure text on webpages,
Escape Constructs وتساعد في صياغة النص الهيكلي على صفحات الويب،
like newlines and special characters.
مثل الخطوط الجديدة والحروف الخاصة.
We want to preserve the structure of the original posting so we
نريد الحفاظ على هيكل الموضع الأصلي، لذا فإننا
won't make note of these as issues to fix in the clean step.
لن ندونها كمشكلة لإصلاحها في خطوة التنظيف.